let questionsList = [
  {
    q_id: 1,
    question: "What is the name of the guitarist of Guns N' Roses?",
    options: [
      { option: "Jimi Hendrix"},
      { option: "Jimmy Page"},
      { option: "Eddie Van Halen"},
      { option: "Slash"}
    ], 
    answer: "Slash"
  },
  {
    q_id: 2,
    question: "What Queen song become a sports anthem in 1977?",
    options: [
      { option: "Stairway to Heaven"},
      { option: "We Will Rock You"},
      { option: "Sweet Child O’ Mine"},
      { option: "TNT"}
    ],
    answer: "We Will Rock You"
  },
  {
    q_id: 3,
    question:"What popular glam-rock band wrote the song ‘Girls Girls Girls’?",
    options: [
      { option: "Helter Skelter"},
      { option: "Jimmy and the News"},
      { option: "Motley Crue"},
      { option: "KISS"}
    ], 
    answer: "Motley Crue"
  },
  {
    q_id: 4,
    question:"What is the first name of the guitarst in Van Halen?",
    options: [
      { option: "Ace Frehley"},
      { option: "Eddie Van Halen"},
      { option: "Brian May"},
      { option: "Stevie Ray Vaughn"}
    ],
    answer: "Eddie Van Halen"
  },
  {
    q_id: 5,
    question:"What is the name of the drummer in Led Zeppelin who died in 1980?",
    options: [
      { option: "Keith Moon"},
      { option: "John Paul Jones"},
      { option: "John Bonham"},
      { option: "Rob Halford"}
    ],
    answer: "John Bonham"
  },
  {
    q_id: 6,
    question:"Out of these heavy metal artists, who has sold the most records worldwide",
    options: [
      { option: "Judas Priest"},
      { option: "Iron Maiden"},
      { option: "Metallica"},
      { option: "Motley Crue"}
    ],
    answer: "Metallica"
  },
  {
    q_id: 7,
    question:"Which one of these Canadian bands does the internet love to hate? ",
    options: [
      { option: "Devin Townsend"},
      { option: "Nickelback"},
      { option: "Justin Bieber"},
      { option: "Drake"}
    ],
    answer: "Nickelback"
  },
  {
    q_id: 8,
    question:"What British band wrote the song Let it Be?",
    options: [
      { option: "The Beatles"},
      { option: "The Rolling Stones"},
      { option: "Queen"},
      { option: "The Clash"}
    ],
    answer: "The Beatles"
  },
  {
    q_id: 9,
    question:"What is the name of the final album that Metallica’s late bassist Cliff Burton played on? ",
    options: [
      { option: "...And Justice For All "},
      { option: "St. Anger"},
      { option: "Ride the Lightning"},
      { option: "Master of Puppets"}
    ],
    answer: "Master of Puppets"
  },
  {
    q_id: 10,
    question:"What is the name of the German artist who released the song Du Hast? ",
    options: [
      { option: "Slipknot"},
      { option: "Static-X"},
      { option: "Oomph!"},
      { option: "Rammstein"}
    ],
    answer: "Rammstein"
  },
];